export const questions = [
    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '木'?", answers: ["モク", "ボク"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '木'?", answers: ["き", "こ"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '語'?", answers: ["ゴ"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '語'?", answers: ["かたる", "かたらう"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '本'?", answers: ["ホン"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '本'?", answers: ["もと"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '彼'?", answers: ["ヒ"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '彼'?", answers: ["かれ", "かの"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '女'?", answers: ["ジョ", "ニョ"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '女'?", answers: ["おんな", "め"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '父'?", answers: ["フ"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '父'?", answers: ["ちち"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '目'?", answers: ["モク", "ボク"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '目'?", answers: ["め", "ま"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '月'?", answers: ["ゲツ", "ガツ"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '月'?", answers: ["つき"] },

    { question: "What is the Onyomi reading of '年'?", answers: ["ネン"] },
    { question: "What is the Kunyomi reading of '年'?", answers: ["とし"] }
];
